- Oh, this is gonna be
the most popular Halloween costume.
- If this is what he does
to make money,
I wanna be Kanye West.
♪ (industrial intro) ♪
- (Adele) 'Cause you know
in the old days,
they couldn't say the [bleep]
they wanted to say.
They had to fake orgasms and [bleep].
- What is this?
- (Adele) "Hey, I wanna
[bleep], [bleep]!"
- What is this?!
- (Adele) We can tell [bleep] today,
"Hey, I wanna..."
- Kanye and Lil Pump.
- There we go, baby!
Ahh! (laughs)
- I hate how much I like this song.
- ♪ You're such a [bleep] ho ♪
♪ I love it ♪
- (gasps) I... (chuckles)
I've seen this all over Twitter,
but I haven't seen it.
- (sings along) ♪ You're such
a [bleep] ho ♪
♪ I love it ♪
- (chuckles)
- ♪ Your boyfriend is a dork,
McLovin ♪
- What the [bleep]?
- ♪ I just pulled up in a Ghost ♪
- It's a catchy song.
I think their outfits are fantastic.
- I don't understand
what this costume is.
- They look like...
What is the video game? Roblox?
- ♪ Ooh, [bleep], she take lines ♪
- I'm very confused.
I'm listening to the words,
trying to get a story line,
and it's nothing.
- ♪ You're such a [bleep] ho ♪
♪ I love it ♪
- I don't know what is going on.
But you know what? I dig it.
- I feel Kanye is onto something,
(laughs) which is why
I don't hate this song.
- (raps along) ♪ I'm a sick [bleep] ♪
♪ I like a quick [bleep], whoop! ♪
- ♪ I'm a sick [bleep] ♪
- Oh, Kanye.
- ♪ I like my [bleep] sucked ♪
♪ I buy you a sick truck ♪
♪ I buy you some new [bleep] ♪
- Oh my... (laughs)
- ♪ How you start a family? ♪
♪ The condom slipped up ♪
- Ah. See, it's like,
I don't wanna like it,
but it's catchy!
- ♪ I like that ho [bleep] ♪
♪ I wanna hear mo' [bleep] ♪
- Kanye say dumb [bleep] all the time,
but when he says
dumb [bleep] in music,
it's just fire.
- ♪ You triflin' ho bitch ♪
♪ Bitch, bitch, bitch ♪
- (snickers)
What's Kanye doing?
- ♪ I love it ♪
- ♪ You're such a [bleep] ho ♪
♪ I love it ♪
- Oh, they're tiny.
Or she's huge.
- (Adele) They had to fake orgasms
and [bleep].
- He got scolded.
- (Adele) "Hey, I wanna [bleep],
[bleep]."
- Okay. I've never seen that before.
- I love it. I'ma ho for this.
I love it.
- I love the song itself and the beat.
The lyrics, though... a little scandy.
I'm trying to look at it
as being sex positive.
- (FBE) So, that was the music video
for "I Love It" by Kanye West
and Lil Pump.
- Oh, is that Lil Pump?
- (FBE) As soon as the video released,
there was a viral frenzy online
of people making various memes
and remixes of that music video.
And so, we've got a few
of those to show you now.
- Okay, I think I'll like this
better than the actual music video.
- (snickers) What the [bleep]?
- Yes, dude! The remake
in Roblox, bro!
- They do look like Roblox.
- ♪ You're such a... ♪
- (Roblox) Oof. Oof.
- (laughs)
- But who has the time to do this?
- I like people that spend
so many hours on such stupid jokes.
- "Kanye and Lil Pump
on the set for "I Love It."
(laughs)
- This is a joke from my generation.
We all know "Doug."
- I haven't thought about that show
in at least 10 years.
- "I can't believe Tom Brady
was in the new Kanye West
and Lil Pump music video." (laughs)
- (amused) He's wearing a coat
over his football pads.
It makes him look square.
That's a good one.
- The second that music video dropped,
everyone was immediately jumping
on the memes.
They did a good job,
because Kanye even retweeted
some of these memes.
♪ (soft piano music) ♪
- I'm not gonna try to guess
the video game,
'cause I don't wanna embarrass myself.
- 'Cause they're Minecraft blocks.
(chuckles) This is so stupid.
- (laughs)
- I was completely thinking
of Minecraft.
- If you come up with a concept
like that, you can't be surprised
there's gonna be some type
of meme that pops up.
- ♪ Like a quick [bleep] ♪
- (laughs)
- ♪ Poopy-di scoop ♪
- Ohhh!
- ♪ Whoop-di-scoop-di-poop ♪
- Whoa, it fits!
- Okay, I actually like that song.
- ♪ Poop-diddy, whoop-scoop ♪
♪ Poop ♪
- This is so dumb!
But it's something so simple
but so good.
- ♪ Whoop-diddy-scoop, poop ♪
- Okay. (laughs) I don't know
what to say about that one.
- "Whoop-diddy, scoop-poop."
-- Kanye, 2018.
- There we go.
Kanye retweeted it!
Gotta do the Roblox version.
- Oh, Kanye tweeted it! Okay.
I think he-- yeah, he probably
knew what he was doing, definitely.
- It's genius. He--
they're just getting free marketing
out of it, right?
So, he's just taking advantage of it
and talking more
about the music video.
- Memes are nice, though,
because one, they give us all
something to relate to,
because we've all seen
this music video,
so we all understand the jokes.
We all like to be in
on the joke.
- (FBE) So, the same day
this music video was released,
users began posting their own videos
of themselves participating
in something like this
using the hashtag, #ILoveItChallenge.
- All of the unnecessary challenges!
- (FBE) So, we have some
of those videos to show you next.
- Interesting. I'm gonna get
some Halloween inspo.
- (laughs) I was thinking,
"How are they gonna look like him?"
But that's accurate.
- Oh, this is gonna be
the most popular Halloween costume.
- I did see this on Twitter!
People are now putting boxes
on themselves
and doing the same [bleep].
- Kanye West is so strategic
in everything that he does.
He strategically makes things
to be outrageous
and for people to just talk about
for days and weeks.
- (chuckles) It's a cardboard box.
- I wanna do that.
I wanna wear a box now.
This is my favorite one so far.
- That's lazy. That's lazy.
You just gonna wear the box?
You not gonna put, like,
a hoodie on it or nothing?
- I like how [bleep]
these are, too.
(laughs) Like, it's just
a cardboard box.
- ♪ She take lines ♪
- These challenges just keep
getting crazier and crazier. (laughs)
- Stupid. And this in particular
is definitely not a challenge,
but they're having fun.
- I would be laughing.
If these are my friends,
I would be pissing my pants laughing.
- I can't imagine being the person
filming this video,
'cause I wouldn't be able to.
I'd be dying of laughter. (laughs)
- (chuckles) Look how happy he is
under that jacket.
- The guy in the silver
is definitely committing more to it.
I'll give him that.
- People can get really creative
with these things.
- This is exactly, though,
what I would like to see on Snapchat
and Insta stories from people.
- The shoes look almost
exactly similar.
- ♪ She take lines, lines ♪
- Now we're talking.
- There we go.
A little more effort, okay.
- That's accurate, see?
That's a great rendition.
- (laughs) I can't.
Why is this a thing?!
I don't get it.
- ♪ ...drinking sparkling water
before you came out here ♪
- Yeah, this is a "challenge"
that'll die really fast.
You're wearing a box,
playing a song, and then moving.
That takes literally no effort.
- Oh! Squad pull up.
That's the best. Ay, ay.
- All right, they're putting
their own little spin on it.
I like it.
- Oh god. Okay, they put in
choreography for this.
I appreciate it a little bit more.
- This is gonna be me and my friends
next time we pull up to a party,
just ready to go. (laughs)
- I'll give them brownie points
for their choreography,
but... just cutting holes in a box
is not enough for me.
- The pictures
and [bleep] were enough.
The roast was enough.
And now, we're out here
putting goddamn boxes on
and dancing,
and it's just like, meh,
that's just boring.
It's just kind of predictable.
- (FBE) So now that you've gotten
a taste of the challenge,
we want you to take on the challenge.
- Oh my god.
- You have a [bleep] box for me
somewhere in here, huh?
All right, bring it!
Come on!
- (FBE) So, in order to do that,
we brought in some special wardrobe
for you to put it on.
- (chuckles)
- (FBE) You ready to do this?
- Cardboard boxes, all right!
- Where is it?
- (FBE) It's right there.
- Nooo! That big box?!
- ♪ ...ho, I love it ♪
- Oh my god. This is actually
harder than I expected.
- ♪ You're such a [bleep] ho ♪
♪ I love it ♪
- (sings along) ♪ I love it ♪
(giggles)
I... hate this.
- This is what he was doing,
right? Kinda.
- ♪ I love it ♪
♪ You're such a... ♪
- I feel like I'm literally as red
as the recording light right now.
- ♪ Your boyfriend is a dork ♪
- This is a really simple challenge.
- ♪ ...McLovin, dork ♪
- (laughs)
- I'm gonna go into a club
wearing this. Just be like, "Ladies,
I love it."
And then I'm gonna get kicked out.
- If this is what he does
to make money,
I wanna be Kanye West.
- (raps along) ♪ I'm a sick [bleep] ♪
♪ I like a quick [bleep] ♪
♪ I like my [bleep] sucked ♪
- ♪ I buy you a sick truck ♪
- That's all I know! (laughs)
I'm sorry, Mom!
- (FBE) So, both the track
and the music video premiered
at the Pornhub Awards...
- (laughs) Yeah!
- (FBE) ...where Kanye served
as creative director
of the award show.
- That is [bleep] hilarious!
- (FBE) And he designed
every presenter's outfit,
and he designed the winning statues
as well as premiering the song
live at the prestigious event.
- Wow! That is so interesting.
- (FBE) But after listening
to this song, why do you think
that they decided to premiere
the track and the music video
at the Pornhub Awards of all places?
- I mean, the lyrics do give
a little bit of a sexy vibe, I guess.
- I feel like for sure
from the both of them,
this was just a joke.
Yeah, we kind of [bleep] around
and made this song.
So yeah, we'll play it
at the Pornhub Awards.
- It's genius cross promotion
from a mental standpoint,
because it's very sex-positive,
and it's all about that.
And then if you're doing it
at the award show for an industry
that's all about sex,
it goes together.
- (FBE) So, critically acclaimed
director Spike Jonze
actually produced the video...
- That, I didn't know.
- (FBE) ...sharing early sketches
of his treatments to reporters.
But the video also features
comedian Adele Givens,
who recites her line
from 2008 Def Comedy Jam stand up
as she towers over the small rappers.
This led some to believe
that even though West and Pump
walk, talk, and dress big,
but when they're facing a woman,
they're just little guys.
- I kind of was getting that
when she's just staring down at them.
- If that's the message we're supposed
to be getting from this, bingo.
But I feel like the attention
is really supposed to still be
on Kanye West and Lil Pump.
- (FBE) After listening to this song
and seeing the music video,
what do you think was the message
that both artists were trying
to get across with this music video?
- Yeah, even if the message was,
oh, men try to really impress women
by puffing up their chests,
but really,
they're these smaller guys,
the message
is completely missed there.
I think people are really
just looking at it objectively
as they're these
weird Roblox characters,
and they're singing
these really [bleep] lyrics.
- Guys were just talking big,
but in reality,
they're much smaller than women.
Even whenever they're calling her--
or her, women, whatever,
a [bleep] ho,
but she's not really,
and she just wants to achieve orgasm
just as much as everyone else does.
- Having a woman in the video
stating her side of things
and, you know, what she feels
about sex positivity
kind of balanced it out.
So, I definitely like
that they included her.
And I think that could've been
the message in this.
- (FBE) So, finally,
like you saw earlier,
the music video immediately started
generating both memes
and challenges online.
- Oh yeah, dude. 60 million views
in five days, yeah.
It has a lot of attention on it.
- (FBE) This is kind
of the second rap song
in recent memory to do this,
like Drake's "In My Feelings"
and "Hotline Bling"
became a huge meme.
Why do you think that all these memes
and challenges are suddenly
coming from hip-hop
and rap music videos specifically?
- I feel like it's probably
because it's very dance-y.
The vibe of the songs,
like, "Hotline Bling"
and "In My Feelings,"
it's just a dance-y song.
And I don't really feel like people
are necessarily reading
into the lyrics.
- A lot of hip-hop tends to set the--
They purposely set
their music up like that.
I remember it being similar--
that kind of way when I was a kid.
There was always the popular dance.
I mean, I remember
in elementary school, for a while
it was the Soulja Boy dance.
- Because internet. (laughs)
I mean, they're just asking
to be... meme-ified.
I guarantee you there somebody
in that office
when they were coming up
with the artistic decor,
and they were like,
"Let's do something that people
are gonna make a meme out of,
because it's gonna extra blow up."
And whoever that was
probably got a raise.
- Thanks for watching this episode
of College Kids React.
And shoutout to Brian White.
- Subscribe so you never
miss an episode.
Shoutout to Sydney Higgins.
- Let us know in the comments
what music video we should
react to next.
- Bye, guys!
- Hey, guys. Ethan here from FBE.
Thank you so much for watching
this episode of College Kids React.
And if you wanna see the reactors
doing more crazy stuff like this,
challenges, gaming, so much more,
you've got to subscribe
to the React Channel, click the link
right over there. Bye, guys.