I DON'T LIKE YOU, T-SERIES
NOTHING PERSONAL KID
BUT I MUST GO ALL OUT
JUST THIS ONCE
BOBS OR VEGANA, WHICHEVER WILL IT BE?
SIT THE FUCK DOWN T-SERIES
I'M HERE TO SPILL THE REAL TEA
YOU TRYNA DETHRONE ME FOR SPOT ON NUMBER ONE?
BUT YOU INDIA YOU LOSE
SO BEST THINK YOU HAVEN'T WON
WHEN I'M THROUGH WITH YOU,
WE'RE GONNA BE COMPLETELY FUCKING DONE
'CAUSE WE ONLY JUST BEGUN!
I'LL REVIEW YOU!
CLAP CLAP
ZERO! BYE BITCH GONE!
SO COME ON T-SERIES!
LOOKING HUNGRY FOR SOME DRAMA????
HERE! LET ME SERVE YOU
BITCH LASAGNA!
T-SERIES AIN'T NOTHING BUT A
BITCH
LASAGNA!
BITCH LASAGNA!
LOOK AT T-SERIES!
THEY JUST CRYING FOR THEIR MAMA!
BITCH LASAGNA!
T-SERIES AIN'T NOTHING BUT A
BITCH
LASAGNA!
BITCH LASAGNA!
T-SERIES JUST WET THEMSELVES IN THEIR PYJAMAS!
SO WHO THE HELL IS BOB AND WHY YOU WANNA KISS HIM?
EWW
I'M A BLUE EYES WHITE DRAGON
WHILE, YOU JUST DARK MAGICIAN
OOF
YOU GOT A FIFTH OF THE POPULATION IN YOUR NATION BUT
I GOT 9 YEAR OLDS OF WORLDS SO HOLD YOUR DEFECATION!
OOPS
MOTU PATLU?
WHAT THE FUCK IS THAT EVEN SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
YOUR LANGUAGE SOUND LIKE IT CAME FROM A MUMBLE RAP COMMUNITY!
NO PAPA!
YES PAPA!
JOHNNY!
NOW DOWN A LOAD-A SUGAR AND
LET'S THROW THIS FUCKING PARTY WITH SOME
BITCH LASAGNA!
BITCH
LASAGNA!
LOOK AT T-SERIES!
THEY JUST CRYING FOR THEIR MAMA!
BITCH
LASAGNA!
T-SERIES AIN'T NOTHING BUT A
BITCH
LASAGNA!
BITCH LASAGNA!
LOOK AT T-SERIES!
THEY JUST WET IN THEIR PYJAMAS!
BITCH LASAGNA!
T-SERIES AIN'T NOTHING BUT A
BITCH
LASAGNA!
YOU GOT A POPULATION OF 1.32 BILLION
BUT MOST YOUR VIDEOS CAN'T SEEM TO HIT EVEN A MILLION
SuB bOt!!1111!111!1!!111!