♪ FEELS LIKE WE'RE ON
THE EDGE RIGHT NOW ♪
♪ I WISH THAT I COULD
SAY I'M PROUD ♪
♪ I'M SORRY THAT I LET
YOU DOWN, LET YOU DOWN ♪
♪ ALL THESE VOICES IN
MY HEAD GET LOUD ♪
♪ I WISH THAT I COULD
SHUT THEM OUT ♪
♪ I'M SORRY THAT I LET
YOU DOWN, LET YOU DOWN ♪
♪ YEAH, I GUESS I'M
A DISAPPOINTMENT ♪
♪ DOING EVERYTHING I
CAN I DON'T WANNA MAKE
YOU DISAPPOINTED ♪
♪ IT'S ANNOYING ♪
♪ I JUST WANNA MAKE YOU
FEEL LIKE EVERYTHING ♪
♪ I EVER DID WAS NEVER TRYIN'
TO MAKE AN ISSUE FOR YOU ♪
♪ BUT I GUESS THE MORE YOU
THOUGHT ABOUT EVERYTHING ♪
♪ YOU WERE NEVER EVEN WRONG
IN THE FIRST PLACE RIGHT ♪
♪ YEAH, I'M A JUST
IGNORE YOU ♪
♪ WALKING TOWARDS YOU
WITH MY HEAD DOWN ♪
♪ LOOKIN' AT THE GROUND
I'M EMBARRASSED FOR YOU ♪
♪ PARANOIA, WHAT DID I
DO WRONG THIS TIME, ♪
♪ THAT'S PARENTS FOR YOU ♪
♪ VERY LOYAL SHOULD
OF HAD MY BACK, ♪
♪ BUT YOU PUT A
KNIFE IN IT ♪
♪ MY HANDS ARE FULL ♪
♪ WHAT ELSE SHOULD I
CARRY FOR YOU ♪
♪ I CARE FOR YOU, BUT ... ♪
♪ FEELS LIKE WE'RE ON
THE EDGE RIGHT NOW ♪
♪ I WISH THAT I COULD
SAY I'M PROUD ♪
♪ I'M SORRY THAT I LET
YOU DOWN, LET YOU DOWN ♪
♪ ALL THESE VOICES IN
MY HEAD GET LOUD ♪
♪ I WISH THAT I COULD
SHUT THEM OUT ♪
♪ I'M SORRY THAT I LET
YOU DOWN, LET YOU DOWN ♪
♪ YEAH, YOU DON'T
WANNA MAKE THIS WORK ♪
♪ YOU JUST WANT TO
MAKE THIS WORSE ♪
♪ WANT ME TO LISTEN TO YOU, ♪
♪ BUT YOU DON'T NEVER
HEAR MY WORDS ♪
♪ YOU DON'T WANT TO
KNOW MY HURT, YEAH ♪
♪ LET ME GUESS YOU WANT
AN APOLOGY PROBABLY ♪
♪ HOW CAN WE KEEP GOING
AT A RATE LIKE THIS ♪
♪ WE CAN'T, SO I GUESS
I'M A HAVE TO LEAVE ♪
♪ PLEASE DON'T
COME AFTER ME, ♪
♪ I JUST WANT TO BE
ALONE RIGHT NOW, ♪
♪ I DON'T REALLY WANT
TO THINK AT ALL ♪
♪ GO AHEAD JUST
DRINK IT OFF, ♪
♪ WE BOTH KNOW YOU GONNA CALL
TOMORROW LIKE NOTHING'S WRONG ♪
♪ AIN'T THAT WHAT
YOU ALWAYS DO, ♪
♪ IT FEELS LIKE EVERY
TIME I TALK TO YOU ♪
♪ YOU'RE IN AN AWFUL MOOD ♪
♪ WHAT ELSE CAN
I OFFER YOU, ♪
♪ THERE'S NOTHING
LEFT RIGHT NOW, ♪
♪ I GAVE IT ALL TO YOU ♪
♪ FEELS LIKE WE'RE ON
THE EDGE RIGHT NOW ♪
♪ I WISH THAT I COULD
SAY I'M PROUD ♪
♪ I'M SORRY THAT I LET
YOU DOWN, LET YOU DOWN ♪
♪ ALL THESE VOICES IN
MY HEAD GET LOUD ♪
♪ I WISH THAT I COULD
SHUT THEM OUT ♪
♪ I'M SORRY THAT I LET
YOU DOWN, LET YOU DOWN ♪
♪ YEAH, DON'T TALK
DOWN TO ME, ♪
♪ THAT'S NOT GONNA
WORK NOW, ♪
♪ PACKED ALL MY CLOTHES,
AND I MOVED OUT ♪
♪ I DON'T EVEN WANT TO
GO TO YOUR HOUSE ♪
♪ EVERY TIME I SIT ON
THAT COUCH I FEEL LIKE
YOU LECTURE ME ♪
♪ EVENTUALLY I BET THAT WE
COULD'VE MADE THIS WORK ♪
♪ AND PROBABLY WOULD'VE
FIGURED THINGS OUT ♪
♪ BUT I GUESS I'M A
LETDOWN, BUT IT'S
COOL I CHECKED OUT ♪
♪ OH, YOU WANNA BE
FRIENDS NOW ♪
♪ OK LET'S PUT MY FAKE
FACE ON AND PRETEND NOW ♪
♪ SIT AROUND AND TALK
ABOUT THE GOOD TIMES THAT
DIDN'T EVEN HAPPEN ♪
♪ I MEAN WHY ARE
YOU LAUGHIN' ♪
♪ MUST'VE MISSED THAT JOKE, LET
ME SEE IF I CAN FIND A REACTION♪
♪ NOPE, BUT AT LEAST
YOU'RE HAPPY ♪
♪ FEELS LIKE WE'RE ON
THE EDGE RIGHT NOW ♪
♪ I WISH THAT I COULD
SAY I'M PROUD ♪
♪ I'M SORRY THAT I LET
YOU DOWN, LET YOU DOWN ♪
♪ ALL THESE VOICES IN
MY HEAD GET LOUD ♪
♪ I WISH THAT I COULD
SHUT THEM OUT ♪
♪ I'M SORRY THAT I LET
YOU DOWN, LET YOU DOWN ♪
♪ I'M SORRY, ♪
♪ I'M SO SORRY OH, ♪
♪ I'M SORRY THAT I LET
YOU DOWN ♪
NATHAN