♪ NO YOU JUST DO YOUR THING ♪
♪ ♪
♪ STOP PLAYING WITH YOUR BODY
LADY ♪
♪ STOP FEELING LIKE
YOU'RE NOT ENOUGH ♪
♪ STOP FEEDING
INTO THE HATERS ♪
♪ STOP AND GIVE YOURSELF
SOME LOVE (WOAH) ♪
♪ STOP STARING AT THE MIRROR
GETTING FADED ♪
♪ SAYING YOU WON'T
FALL IN LOVE ♪
♪ STOP TRUSTING ALL THOSE
FAKE IDIOTS ♪
♪ TRUST ME THEY DON'T
GIVE A FUCK (WOAH) ♪
♪ I'M TIRED OF SEEING IT ♪
♪ I'M TIRED OF FEELING THIS ♪
♪ THE WORLD SAYS BEAUTY IS
CHANGING ♪
♪ FUCK THAT IT'S FAKE
EXPECTATION OF THE REAL SHIT ♪
♪ LET'S GET NAKED ♪
♪ START MEDITATING
FEEL ELEVATED AND SAY ♪
♪ I LOVE MY BODY
I LOVE MY SKIN ♪
♪ I AM A GODDESS
I AM A QUEEN ♪
♪ I LOVE MY BODY
I LOVE MY SKIN ♪
♪ I AM A GODDESS
I AM A QUEEN ♪
♪ STOP CHASING ALL THE HYPE,
MY GIRL ♪
♪ STOP TRYING TO CHANGE
WHO YOU ARE ♪
♪ STOP CUTTING YOURSELF UP
ON THE OUTSIDE (OUTSIDE) ♪
♪ WHEN THE INSIDE
IS NEVER SCARRED ♪
♪ IT CAN'T BE HEALED WITH
SOMETHING MATERIALISTIC ♪
♪ CAN'T BE HEALED BY A
MAN WHO STAYS DISTANT ♪
♪ IT'S DEEPER ♪
♪ SAVE YOURSELF
BEFORE YOU BETRAY YOURSELF ♪
♪ OOH OOH ♪
♪ I'M TIRED OF SEEING IT
(SO TIRED) ♪
♪ I'M TIRED OF FEELING THIS ♪
♪ THE WORLD SAYS
BEAUTY IS CHANGING ♪
♪ FUCK THAT IT'S FAKE
EXPECTATION OF THE REAL SHIT ♪
♪ LET'S GET NAKED
(LET'S GET NAKED) ♪
♪ START MEDITATING
FEEL ELEVATED AND SAY ♪
♪ I LOVE MY BODY
I LOVE MY SKIN ♪
♪ I AM A GODDESS
I AM A QUEEN ♪
♪ I LOVE MY BODY
I LOVE MY SKIN ♪
♪ I AM A GODDESS
I AM A QUEEN ♪
♪ YES ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I LOVE MY BODY
I LOVE MY SKIN ♪
♪ I AM A GODDESS
I AM A QUEEN ♪
♪ I LOVE MY BODY
I LOVE MY SKIN ♪
♪ I AM A GODDESS
I AM A QUEEN ♪
♪ I LOVE MY
I LOVE MY ♪
♪ I AM A
I AM A ♪
♪ I LOVE MY,
I LOVE MY (HUH) ♪
♪ I AM A
I AM A ♪
♪ I LOVE MY BODY
I LOVE MY SKIN ♪
♪ I AM A GODDESS
I AM A QUEEN ♪
♪ I LOVE MY BODY
I LOVE MY SKIN (YEAH) ♪
♪ I AM A GODDESS
I AM A QUEEN ♪
♪ HMM ♪
♪ I AM A QUEEN
QUEEN, QUEEN ♪
♪ I AM A QUEEN ♪
♪ I AM QUEEN ♪
♪ ♪
♪ (LAUGHING) ♪