♪ I WALK ON WATER ♪
♪ BUT I AIN'T NO JESUS ♪
♪ BUT ONLY WHEN IT FREEZES ♪
♪ WHY ARE EXPECTATIONS
SO HIGH? ♪
♪ IS IT THE BAR I SET? ♪
♪ MY ARMS I STRETCH BUT I CAN'T
REACH A FAR CRY FROM IT ♪
♪ OR ITS IN MY GRASP BUT AS SOON
AS I GRAB SQUEEZE ♪
♪ I LOSE MY GRIP LIKE
THE FLYING TRAPEZE ♪
♪ INTO THE DARK I PLUMMET ♪
♪ NOW THE SKY'S BLACKENING ♪
♪ I KNOW THE MARKS HIGH BUTTA' ♪
♪ FLY'S RIP APART MY STOMACH ♪
♪ KNOWIN' THAT NO MATTER WHAT
BARS I COME WITH ♪
♪ YOU'RE GONNA HARP GRIPE AND ♪
♪ THAT'S A HARD VICODIN
TO SWALLOW ♪
♪ SO I SCRAP THESE ♪
♪ AS PRESSURE INCREASES
LIKE KHAKI'S ♪
♪ I FEEL THE ICE
CRACKING BECAUSE ♪
♪ I WALK ON WATER ♪
♪ BUT I AIN'T NO JESUS ♪
♪ I WALK ON WATER (SHIT) ♪
♪ BUT ONLY WHEN IT FREEZES ♪
♪ IT'S THE CURSE OF
THE STANDARD ♪
♪ THAT THE FIRST OF THE
MATHERS DISC SET ♪
♪ ALWAYS IN SEARCH OF THE VERSE
THAT I HAVEN'T SPIT YET ♪
♪ WILL THIS STEP JUST BE
ANOTHER MISSTEP ♪
♪ TO TARNISH WHATEVER THE LEGACY
LOVE OR RESPECT ♪
♪ I'VE GARNERED ♪
♪ THE RHYME HAS
TO BE PERFECT ♪
♪ THE DELIVERY FLAWLESS ♪
♪ AND IT ALWAYS FEEL'S LIKE I'M
HITTIN' THE MARK ♪
♪ 'TIL I GO SIT IN THE CAR
LISTEN & PICK IT APART ♪
♪ LIKE THIS SHIT IS GARBAGE ♪
♪ GOD'S GIVEN ME ALL THIS ♪
♪ STILL I FEEL NO
DIFFERENT REGARDLESS ♪
♪ KIDS LOOK TO ME AS A GOD
THIS IS RETARDED ♪
♪ IF ONLY THEY KNEW IT'S A
FAÇADE AND IT'S EXHAUSTIVE ♪
♪ AND I TRY NOT TO
LISTEN TO NONSENSE ♪
♪ BUT IF YOU BITCHES
ARE TRYIN' ♪
♪ TO STRIP ME OF MY CONFIDENCE ♪
♪ MISSION ACCOMPLISHED ♪
♪ I'M NOT GOD SENT ♪
♪ NAS, RAKIM, PAC, BIG,
JAMES TODD SMITH ♪
♪ AND I'M NOT PRINCE SO ♪
♪ I WALK ON WATER ♪
♪ BUT I AIN'T NO JESUS ♪
♪ BUT ONLY WHEN IT FREEZES ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I'M ONLY HUMAN
JUST LIKE YOU ♪
♪ MAKIN' MY MISTAKES OH IF YOU
ONLY KNEW ♪
♪ I DON'T THINK YOU SHOULD
BELIEVE IN ME ♪
♪ THE WAY THAT YOU DO 'CAUSE ♪
♪ I'M TERRIFIED TO LET
YOU DOWN, OH ♪
♪ IT'S TRUE I'M A RUBIK'S A
BEAUTIFUL MESS ♪
♪ AT TIMES JUVENILE YES I GOOF
AND I JEST ♪
♪ A FLAWED HUMAN I GUESS ♪
♪ BUT I'M DOIN' MY BEST ♪
♪ TO NOT RUIN
YOUR EXPECTATIONS ♪
♪ AND MEET 'EM BUT FIRST THE
"SPEEDOM" VERSE ♪
♪ NOW BIG SEAN
HE'S GOIN' TO FAST ♪
♪ IS HE GONNA SHOUT OR
CURSE OUT HIS MOM ♪
♪ THERE WAS A TIME I HAD THE
WORLD BY THE BALLS ♪
♪ EATIN' OUT MY PALM ♪
♪ EVERY ALBUM SONG ♪
♪ I WAS SPAZIN' THE
FUCK OUT ON AND ♪
♪ NOW I'M GETTIN' CLOWNED
AND FROWNED ON ♪
♪ BUT THE ONLY ONE WHO'S
LOOKING DOWN ON ME ♪
♪ THAT MATTERS NOW'S DESHAUN ♪
♪ AM I LUCKY TO BE
AROUND THIS LONG ♪
♪ BEGS THE QUESTION THOUGH
ESPECIALLY AFTER THE METHADONE ♪
♪ AS YESTERDAY FADES AND
THE DRESDEN HOME ♪
♪ IS BURNT TO THE
GROUND AND ALL ♪
♪ THAT'S LEFT OF MY
HOUSE IS LAWN ♪
♪ THE CROWDS ARE GONE ♪
♪ AND IT'S TIME TO WASH
OUT THE BLOND ♪
♪ SALES DECLINE THE
CURTAINS DRAWN ♪
♪ THERE CLOSIN' THE SET ♪
♪ I'M STILL POKIN' MY HEAD
FROM OUT BEHIND ♪
♪ AND EVERYONE WHO HAS
DOUBT REMIND ♪
♪ NOW TAKE YOUR BEST
RHYME OUT DO IT ♪
♪ NOW DO IT A THOUSAND TIMES ♪
♪ NOW LET 'EM TELL
YA THE WORLD ♪
♪ NO LONGER CARES OR GIVES A
FUCK ABOUT YOUR RHYMES ♪
♪ AND AS I GROW OUT OF SIGHT
OUT OF MIND ♪
♪ I MIGHT GO OUTTA MINE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE HOW DO I ♪
♪ EVER LET THIS MIC GO
WITHOUT A FIGHT ♪
♪ WHEN I MADE A FUCKIN'
TIGHTROPE OUTTA TWINE ♪
♪ BUT WHEN I DO FALL ♪
♪ FROM THESE HEIGHTS
THOUGH I'LL BE FINE ♪
♪ I WON'T POUT OR CRY OR
SPIRAL DOWN OR WHINE ♪
♪ BUT I'LL DECIDE IF IT'S
MY FINAL BOW ♪
♪ THIS TIME AROUND/'CAUSE ♪
♪ I WALK ON WATER ♪
♪ BUT I AIN'T NO JESUS ♪
♪ BUT ONLY WHEN IT FREEZES ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I'M ONLY HUMAN
JUST LIKE YOU ♪
♪ AND MAKIN' MY MISTAKES
OH IF YOU ONLY KNEW ♪
♪ I DON'T THINK YOU SHOULD
BELIEVE IN ME ♪
♪ THE WAY THAT YOU DO ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I'M TERRIFIED TO
LET YOU DOWN ♪
♪ OH IF I WALKED ON WATER
I WOULD DROWNED ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I'M JUST A MAN BUT
AS LONG AS I GOT A MIC ♪
♪ I'M GOD LIKE SO ME AND YOU
ARE NOT ALIKE ♪
♪ BITCH I WROTE STAN ♪