I'm not sure if you're my... Uh... Uber but i'll give you 20 Bucks if you wanna take me to my destination instead of the Taxi.
Can I rap for you?
What?
Yo what up, man?
Yo what up? (laughing)
Whew, there's lights in here!
I gotta make sure not to drive to fast here.
So uh do you youngyins like uh rap music?
(laughing)
Would it be cool if I busted a rap?
Yeah.
Is it chilly in here?
Nah, it's good.
Okay it's about to be ice cold, so
*Rap God by Eminem starts playing*
O!O! (excited)
You know, this beat's kinda too slow for me.
Let's speed that shit up!
*GRANDPA  STARTS RAPPING*
*RAPPING CONTINUES*
Oh, I think I'm gonna have a heart attack.
Aah dude thats great (laughing) that is great
nice to meet you guys
Guys, no, no how, many people cancel just by seeing me they're like
Hey, guys, thanks so much for watching the video if you liked it make sure you give it a
Thumbs up just comment let me know, what you think i know it's been a long time, since i've released a big video
Like this, but i'm glad, to say that i'm back, yo make sure you, subscribe
watch all, my other videos do little dance and
peace out yo
Whoa i almost fell